[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What body part of the giraffe can indicate its gender?", "correct_answer": "Horns", "incorrect_answers": ["Tongue", "Teeth", "Eyes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Titanium melts at 1941\u00b0 on what temperature scale?", "correct_answer": "Kelvin", "incorrect_answers": ["Newton", "Fahrenheit", "Celsius"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which team won the second World Series between the National League and the American League?", "correct_answer": "New York Giants", "incorrect_answers": ["Pittsburgh Pirates", "Providence Grays", "New York Metropolitans"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who wrote the novels on which the Bourne movies are based?", "correct_answer": "Robert Ludlum", "incorrect_answers": ["John La Carre", "William Blake Herron", "Robert Gilroy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This class of enzyme can cut DNA at a specific place, making biotechnology possible.", "correct_answer": "Restriction Enzyme", "incorrect_answers": ["Bayton Enzyme", "Electrophoretic Enzyme", "Limiting Enzyme"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where can an asteroid belt, a region of greatest concentration of orbiting asteroids, be found nearest to Earth?", "correct_answer": "Between Mars and Jupiter", "incorrect_answers": ["Between Jupiter and Saturn", "Between Uranus and Neptune", "Beyond Pluto"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which is the most bitter substance known to taste researchers?", "correct_answer": "Denatonium", "incorrect_answers": ["Quinine", "Brucine", "Coffee"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the chemical symbol for Vanadium?", "correct_answer": "V", "incorrect_answers": ["Va", "Vn", "Vd"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Today people visit Colorado to go skiing, hiking, mountain biking and to enjoy the scenery. But 100 years ago, tourists more often went to the mountains to do what?", "correct_answer": "Soak in hot springs", "incorrect_answers": ["Play golf", "Record music", "Go horseback riding"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the black color associated with in Native American tradition?", "correct_answer": "Soil", "incorrect_answers": ["Storms", "War", "Death"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What toy is a must-have gift in the comedy movie Jingle All the Way, starring Arnold Schwarzenegger?", "correct_answer": "Turbo-Man", "incorrect_answers": ["Action-Man", "Sinbad", "Dementor"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the only mass extinction in which insects were affected?", "correct_answer": "Permian/Triassic event", "incorrect_answers": ["Cretaceous/Paleogene event", "Ordovician/Silurian event", "Triassic/Jurassic event"]}]